{
    "subject": "resource/RuPaul",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/California",
    "human_readable": "RuPaul was born in California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9134578704833984,
            "question": "Where was RuPaul born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9118598103523254,
            "question": "Is RuPaul originally from California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.830142617225647,
            "question": "Does RuPaul have any other notable accomplishments besides being born in California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7349429726600647,
            "question": "Has RuPaul ever spoken about his upbringing in California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6282779574394226,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from California who are similar to RuPaul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5673778653144836,
            "question": "What state is RuPaul from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5196576118469238,
            "question": "What are some iconic locations in California that RuPaul might have visited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46181586384773254,
            "question": "What is RuPaul known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4272323548793793,
            "question": "What is the significance of being born in California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2672262489795685,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about RuPaul's early life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=RuPaul was born in California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7653_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of being born in California?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7653_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is RuPaul known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7653_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some iconic locations in California that RuPaul might have visited?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7653_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7653_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7653_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7653_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7653_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7653_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7653_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7653_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7653_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7653_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7653_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that RuPaul Andre Charles (known as RuPaul) was born in San Diego, California."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}